We're back with Bethany Frankel, and switching gears a little bit, so you took your daughter, your precious little genius daughter, to, Bren, to Disney World.
Had she been before?
She had been to Disneyland here, and I had an appearance to do for Skinny World Cocktails down there, which was weird going down to the happiest place on Earth during the middle of the hurricane.
This was every princess, Tinkerbell, Snow White.
We did the whole thing.
We did the lunch at the Princess Castle.
Jason was like, the food's really good.
And he's saying, imagine me out with my guy friends being like, that pasta was amazing in Orlando.
And they'd be like, where?
He'd be like, Princess Castle.
Princesses are everything.
And I literally, you know, I'm not really jaded when I meet celebrities.
I mean, when I meet celebrities, I am jaded.
Because I'll, you know, I've met them.
And I don't get all freaked out.
You're like, Jasmine's coming!
Hurry up!
Like, you freak out.
Prince, get over here with your autographed buckets.
Hurry up!
Like, you're crazy.
Because it's Disney.
And the characters are important.
And you don't get it.
They don't see them that often.
Like a Mickey Mouse.
Mickey Mouse.
Mickey Mouse doesn't come out that often.
Just so you know, you don't walk around Disney.
He only hangs out on Main Street.
He's not like running around accessible.
He's a celebrity.
What is wrong with you?
No, he is.
It's a big deal when you're there.
They're people dressed in costumes.
No, they're not.
No, and they don't break.
No, they're not, Ellen.
They don't break character ever?
Never.
I said to Arielle, didn't we see you before?
Because now she was in her gown after she married the prince and before she was in her mermaid outfit and looked like the same face half hour ago.
She goes, no, my daddy just gave me legs for my birthday.
No, they do not break, Ellen.
But I think that they do at night.
I think there's like a Disney after hours.
You know what I mean?
Princess has gone wild.
Oh, I'm sure.
If you know what I mean.
It gets ugly early, you know?
I'm sure.
Yes.
And everything is Mickey Mouse.
The carpet has Mickey Mouse in it.
And the shower heads are Mickey Mouse.
And you're like in the Mickey Mouse cult.
I asked someone for mint.
And I swear to you, it was shaped like a mouse.
All right.
Are you excited about your talk show in the fall?
You must be excited.
You're getting close.
I'm very excited.
I am very excited.
I cannot wait.
Are we doing it here or in New York?
What have we decided?
We haven't decided yet.
We haven't decided.
All right, because I haven't heard the latest.
I know.
We haven't decided yet.
It's the kind of thing that it's going to be great no matter where it is.
It's not what you're doing.
It's who you're with.
And it's not where you are, but it's who you're with.
Or it's not where you are, but it's what you're doing.
What?
Are you going to be able to work the rest of the day after this?
I think I've freed you out a little bit.
Thank god it's over.
I want to thank Russell Brand and Hyundai.
And their Hope on Wheels program has funded over 300 research projects to help find a cure for pediatric cancer.
Bethany Frankel, I will see you tomorrow.
Be kind to one another.
Thank you.
Bye bye.